

# Luis Eduardo Urdaneta Martucci

Full-Stack Web App Developer

LuisEUM95@gmail.com

+34 611 13 20 50

www.linkedin.com/in/luiseum



@LuisEUM



https://github.com/LuisEUM



https://alkitu.com

## SUMMARY

Web developer, graphic designer, and digital marketing specialist with more than 2 years of experience in each field. I founded a freelancer business during the quarantine where I led teams on more than 15 large projects in France, Spain, USA, and Morocco. I make businesses and projects reach their full growth potential with my multidisciplinary skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep. 2022 - Present

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya - Spain Digital Interaction and Multimedia Techniques Degree

Apr. 2022 - Oct. 2022 IronHack - Spain Web Development FullStack

Intensive Bootcamp to learn the full MERN stack.

Sep. 2012 - Mar. 2017

Universidad Simón Bolívar - Venezuela Bachelor's Degree in International Bussiness

# **SKILLS**

- MongoDB
- Express JS
- React JS Node JS
- .ISX
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS
- Framer Motion Prisma
- **AuthJS** Zod
- **ESlint**
- Shadcn/UI
- Puppeteer
- Postman **TypeScript**
- JavaScript (ES6)
- HTML5
- CSS<sub>3</sub>

- Bootstrap
- Handlehars
- **RESTful APIs** GitHub
- WordPress
- SEO
- **SEM**
- Google Ads
- Google Tag Manager
- Google Search Console
- Google Analytics
- UX/ŬI
- Figma
- Adobe Photoshops
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Indesign
- Adobe After Effects
- Microsft office
- Social Media

# LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Fluent

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **INSIDE HAIR - Spain**

Sep. 2023 - Present

## iT Manager

I developed and designed the Full Stack web application using NextJS. Additionally, I optimized and maintained non-relational databases, improved the no-code web platform in WordPress, provided continuous technical support to the team and clients, enhanced the security of the company's digital resources, as well as created and maintained various tools and databases in Excel.

Techs: Next.js 14 + TailwindCSS + ESLint + TypeScript + Shadon/UI + Prisma + MongoDB + AuthJS + React Hook Form + Zod + TanStack Table

#### Tangle - Netherlands

Nov. 2022 - Feb. 2023

Web Developer

Tangle Offline Website: Repository & Web

Techs: NextJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion, and ESlint.

InstagramScraper - API RESTful: Repository

Techs: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Puppeteer, and Postman

# Bootcamp Ironhack - Spain

Apr. 2022 - Oct. 2022

Web Developer

Gousty The Ghost - Desktop Game: Repository & Web

Techs: CSS3, HTML5, and JavaScript (ES6)

BIG MENU - Menu creator: Repository & Web

Techs: MongoDB, ExpressJS, NodeJS, Handlebars, and Bootstrap

Top Top - Restaurant Network: Repository & Web Techs: MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap, and Framer Motion

#### Alkitu - Spain

Mar. 2020 - Present

#### Freelancer and Founder

Designed and developed brands, webs, and advertising material. Improved companies with digital marketing strategies, and led a team of freelancers serving over 30 clients from different countries.

#### La Plataforma Publicitaria - Spain Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2021

# Administrative Assistant/Graphic Designer

Analyzed, prepared, and designed the brands, digital advertising material, and printing material of more than 200 clients.

#### OcasionPlus, S. L. - Spain

Jan. 2019 - Nov. 2021

#### Administrative Assistant/Photographer

Teamed with another photographer and took pictures, edited, and published over 1.000 cars in 3 different stores in Valencia.

# L'etiquette eventos - Ecuador

Jun. 2017 - Jun. 2018

Community Manager

Planned and created the content and copy for social media channels; social media following grew 2300%+ organically in a year.

#### Grupo MANTRA® - Ecuador

Jun. 2016 - Nov 2016

**Marketing Department Intern** 

Developed and executed a marketing plan with extensive product testing and validation, resulting in successful negotiations with Walt Disney and sales of over 5000 units in a month to top chains in Ecuador.